SHELDON PASCIAK

sheldon@pasciak.com

OBJECTIVE:

Position as a web programmer on a team where experience and education combine to provide the most effective, creative and professional results.

CAREER SUMMARY:

Proficiency in application development using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, JQuery, and Microsoft .NET; Experience using SQL and Postgres database technologies; Maintains and develops independent web based applications using JQuery and Node-JS technology; Superior leadership and communication skills gained through over 20 years of military service.

EDUCATION:

B.S., Information Technology, Daytona State College, expected graduation, May 2017. GPA 4.0 on a 4.0 scale, Dean's List, President's List

A.A., Liberal Arts, Joliet Junior College, December 2012. GPA 3.9 on a 4.0 scale, Dean's List, President's List

RELATED EXPERIENCE:

Administrative Supervisor, Information Technology Operator-Analyst, U.S. Army, 1990-2011

Created and implemented web applications using SQL server to provide attendance tracking for over 1,500 students daily. Automated numerous processes to support knowledge management initiatives within NATO Headquarters.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY:

Technician / Vendor, City of Daytona Beach, November 2015 – Present.

Volunteer, Halifax Habitat for Humanity, January 2013 - June 2013.

Security Office Supervisor, U.S. Army, 52nd Signal Battalion, Stuttgart, Germany, 2009-2011.

Information Technology Instructor, U.S. Army, 15th Signal Brigade, Augusta, Georgia, 2007-2009.

Information Assurance Analyst, Directorate of Information Management, Augusta, Georgia, 2005-2007.

Dear Sir or Ma'am:

A recent query for job openings at Monster.com alerted me to your search for a Web Programmer that will test, develop, maintain, and support software systems. My experience as a software developer for over 10 years, along with the skills I'm learning while pursuing a Bachelor's Degree in Information Technology, make me an excellent addition to your team.

My passion for computer software stems from my need to innovate and improve existing systems. Throughout my career as an Information Systems Operator-Analyst in the U.S. Army, I sought ways to automate processes by creating new software to meet a variety of needs. Currently, I continue to create and maintain independent web programs of my own. These applications use the latest technologies and provide me with an environment to continually build my skills. I look forward to the opportunity to work with others to create innovative solutions that are effective, creative and professionally polished.

Please review the enclosed résumé for additional information regarding my reliability, experience, and skills. I look forward to talking with you about how my education and experience can benefit your company and its customers in the future.